

Michael Hutchinson

Frontend Software Developer



+44 7528 283 656



michael-hutchinson@hotmail.co.uk

Skills

- JavaScript (ES6)
- · React, Typescript, NextJS
- GraphQL
- Cypress.io
- Jest, React Testing Library
- AWS
- Storybook
- TailwindCSS, Styled Components,
- Prisma, MongoDB
- Redux
- Monetate AB Testing

Hobbies & Interest











Social

github.com/michael-hutchinson





References

Available on request

About

Over the last year 7 years I have built on my solid academic background in Computer Science with exposure to Frontend Development, UX Design as well as Agile ways of working for start-ups, leading retail brands and large software houses.

Education

2012 - 2016 Leeds Beckett University 2016 - 2017 **BSc Hons Computer Science MSc Information & Technology**

Experience



Thrive Learning Limited

Frontend Developer | March 2022 - Present

Working in a Scrum team to deliver new features for our bespoke learning platform.

Tech: React / Typescript / Redux / GraphQL / SASS / Storybook / Cypress / Jest / React Testing Library / AWS / Jira / React Native.



Cheshire Data systems Limited

Senior Web Developer | December 2019 - February 2022

Part of a multi-disciplined Kanban Squad. Working on projects to improve our customers user journeys for car, home and pet insurance.

Tech: React / JavaScript / SASS / Docker / JSP / Jenkins / Cypress / Maven / Gulp / XML / JSON / Jira / AWS / React Native.



Boohoo Limited

UX Executive | June 2019 - December 2019

I worked in a self sufficient UX team focusing on maximising the boohoo brand. Creating UI designs, high and low level designs and creating A/B tests.

Tech: AdobeXD / Figma / Photoshop / JavaScript / AB Testing.



Cheshire Data systems Limited

Frontend Web Developer | October 2018 - June 2019

Worked in a scrum team delivering web products for new and existing clients. This multi-disciplined digital delivery squad created tech in the insurance sector.

Tech: React / JavaScript / SASS / Docker / JSP / Jenkins / Cypress / Maven / Gulp / XML / JSON / Jira.



Relative Connections Limited

Junior Web Developer | October 2017 - October 2018

Building web applications for in house brands. Focusing on user retention and experience. Role involved creating new landing pages and re-branding sister brands.

Tech: HTML / CSS / JQuery / JavaScript / Wordpress / PHP / Bootstrap / Git.



AETC Limited

Junior Web Developer | June 2014 - August 2015

Placement year part of my university course. A great opportunity to work for a large scale engineering company in their IT team. Tech: HTML / CSS / JQuery / JavaScript / Bootstrap / Git.